it's you i found you you're her aren't you you're my old friend i can't believe it
i loved you so much didn't we take a photo together i remember we drank some honey ginger
milk that mom made for us and then we sang the love song why didn't you say anything
you're warm you must still have a fever
that pendant was mom's why do you have it when the only one who could is the bear that killed her
what's going on
I was once unwanted. A lonely bear cub. Abandoned in the human world.
I found you.
That was when I met him.
Don't worry, I'll shelter you. This school is my box.
He really, really liked boxes.
My dear Eureka, it's important for you to understand that this world sullies anything pure.
Here. If I do this, the flower will be able to stay unsullied for the rest of eternity.
You see, in this world, only the unsullied have value.
You're incredibly beautiful, Eureka. And you're so special. The most especially precious treasure I own.
I allowed him to put me into his box. And I was happy there. As long as I stayed inside his box, I was an especially precious unsullied creature.
I was unwanted no more. But then, one day...
I'm afraid I found my next wonderfully unsullied creature. So, I'm leaving.
Wait, wait! Please, my precious one! Please don't abandon me here!
Grrrr-aa-aa-aa-aa-aa-aa-aa-aa-aa-aa-aa-aa-aa-aa-aa!
K'nushak!
In that moment, I learned the truth.
I understood what he was trying to teach me.
You must box up what is precious to you.
Otherwise, they'll walk right out of your life and wind up sullied.
From now on, this school is my box.
Why are you cutting them down?
I have to cut all these blooms before they get sullied.
If not, I can't put them in a box.
Why would you want to box them up?
So I can protect these pure precious things from the world.
If I protect all the things that are precious to me, then I will be special.
Because if I am not special...
If I am unwanted, no one will find me.
I found you.
You found me? Are you sure?
Yes.
So get out of that box of yours.
If you never open the box and see and touch your precious collection,
then you might as well just not have anything at all.
Might as well not.
Do you feel empty too?
Like the whole world is invisible?
Open up your boxes.
I'd love it if you'd show me what is truly precious to you.
And so, Rhea and I became the best of friends.
She gave color to my blank, invisible world.
Everything changed.
I found all sorts of precious and wonderful things when I was with Rhea.
She allowed herself to be sullied with me, and I was honored.
Rhea.
I want to say...
I need to say...
I love you.
Rhea?
Do you love me too?
Yes.
I love you so much.
And we'll be friends forever, won't we?
Yes.
Forever and ever.
Rhea.
Yes?
Happy birthday.
Yuri Ika.
I thought the perfect gift would be to have proof of our friendship.
A pledge to never forget love.
As long as you don't forget love, you'll never, ever be truly alone.
And if you never give up on love, even if you lose something, you'll never be invisible.
Rhea.
I love you.
Oh, I love you so much.
I knew all along that Rhea's love was different from mine.
I knew it.
But I couldn't help myself.
I wallowed in that sweet, fleeting desire.
And it was beautiful.
Her name is Kureha.
It means red wing.
She's perfect, don't you think?
Let that go.
It seems she went suspended for herself.
Isn't that sweet?
Sweet.
Now, Kureha, say hi to one of Mama's best friends in the whole wide world.
See?
Did I not tell you as much?
You must box up all your precious things.
Otherwise, they'll be sullied and you'll lose them.
Now, Rhea's love has been lost.
That baby took it away and it's your fault.
You left your box like a fool and became sullied.
Babies are perfect.
They're among the purest things in this filthy world.
No more.
I will give up on love.
I'm sullied, so I'm dirty and empty.
I am invisible.
I am not precious enough for someone to box up anymore.
So now, I am a box.
I've become an empty box, wishing for something to fill my void.
The stars rained down.
The world was still invisible.
Then, the wall of severance was formed.
And now, we can never go back again.
Never.
Rhea.
Complete me.
I need you to fill in my gaps.
I'm so lonely.
Please, Rhea.
Please, help me.
Rhea.
Take this pendant with you, sweetie.
It's a love charm.
I know it will help you the way it helped me.
Rhea.
Why did you give your pendant away?
Do you love her instead of me?
No.
She's just Rhea's friend.
Is she?
I don't care.
You threw the proof of our friendship away.
Rhea.
You threw my love away.
I ate Rhea.
I wanted to put her in the box of myself.
Surely that would complete me.
At least, that's what I thought.
Even after eating Rhea, I felt starved.
The emptiness inside me still wasn't filled.
Before I knew it, I found myself interrogating her.
Good for you?
Did she have an excuse at all?
Well...
The night my mom was killed by a bear, the pendant she was wearing disappeared.
Why in the world do you have it, Ginko?
Not right now.
The only thing she would say was she couldn't tell me right then.
And when I woke up this morning, both of them had left without saying goodbye.
What are these?
This is the evidence we need to prove they're actually bears disguised as humans.
And as for that Ginko Yurishiro one, she's the bear with Rhea's pendant.
You think she's the bear that killed mom?
Yes.
Of that I have no doubt.
Oh no.
You were young.
She got close to you by saying she was your friend.
Then she took away the most precious thing in your life.
She murdered your mother.
We can't expect love or friendship from them.
They must be excluded.
Excluded?
That's right.
And by the way,
since you stole Rhea's love from me,
that crime will have to be paid for with your flesh.
There's no escaping now, Kurei Asubaki.
You're going to be my bride.
My bride in the box.
Ginko Yurishiro,
I know all about the grave crime you committed.
I know what you did.
You are the one who...
Hey, Ginko.
How about we go back to the other side of the wall?
Lulu doesn't think it matters how true your love is.
When she knows you're a bear,
growl,
Kurei Pai won't forgive you.
Promise kisses only exist in picture books.
Kumariya is the goddess of the wall.
Her job is to separate bears and humans.
She never let us all be friends.
I made you give up on kisses for me, Lulu.
I can't go back to our side now.
Growl, growl.
Even if it means a grave sin?
Lulu knows what you did, Ginko,
so please,
let's just go home.
If Kurei Pai finds out the whole truth,
you'll never get love.
But you won't be able to do a promise kiss
without telling her the whole truth.
Come on, let's go home.
Even if you give up on love,
Lulu will still love you.
Lulu doesn't care if she can't ever kiss,
just so long as you're with her.
But,
Lulu, I...
Yes.
Is your love the real thing?
Absolutely.
This is a challenge from the wall of Severance.
Kurei Ha, Tsubaki,
if your love is true,
go to the roof immediately.
The bears are waiting for you.
I'm on my way.
We were friends.
Yes, I loved her, but...
I'll never forgive those bears.
I'll ruin them.
Everyone!
Wait!
Please, Ginko!
Lulu really doesn't mind
if you love Kurei Pai, Growl!
Just don't leave her!
Please don't go!
Ginko!
Give yourself over to the humans,
and your love will be approved.
I'm so sorry, Lulu.
Ginko!
Growl!
She's so cool.
However,
I'm not entirely sure
this was the right thing to do.
Don't be so dramatic.
We're only doing what has to be done
in order to find out whose love is true.
Sparkle, Sparkle, Sparkle.
But it still seems horribly cruel.
Order in the court, please.
We swell here
in the space between human and bear.
Everything must be done
according to Kumaria's will,
for that is sexy.
Perhaps it will rain,
Shabagami.
The time has come at last.
Come to me, Kurei Ha-Subaki.
After all,
I cast aside Beardom to become human,
and I did it for you.
Defendant Bear Yiriyika Hakonaka,
I ask you,
will you give up on boxes,
or will you give up on love?
I will never give up on boxes,
so I'll give up on love.
Please, make me human.
I'd like to be there
to see Kurei Ha-Subaki grow up.
Rhea's love is still alive
inside that girl.
And I want to fill up
the box of myself
with that love.
Are you sure you won't regret that?
You realize if you were given
what you ask for,
you'll be doomed to be a box
for all eternity.
Rhea gave my love away
to some other cub
like it was nothing,
and I've made the choice
to hold it against her.
I'd rather be a box
than forgive.
I see.
I shall now declare the verdict.
Yuri, approved!
Miss Yurieika,
you're here?
I've been waiting for you,
sweet Kurei Ha.
What for?
You'll find her over there.
It's you, Ginko.
Be careful.
Remember,
she is the bear
who killed Rhea.
She is our mortal enemy.
You killed my mother!
Take her out.
Ginko betrayed both of you.
I know she claimed
to be your friend,
but it was just a trick.
A trick she used
to take away
what was most precious to you.
Kurei Ha.
You ate my mother!
How could you do
something like that?
I didn't eat her,
Growl, Growl.
Yes, you did!
Why else would you
be wearing her pendant?
Your mother gave it to me.
She said it was a love charm.
She gave you a love charm?
I am a bear.
But somehow,
we still managed
to be friends,
Growl, Growl.
Until one day,
you and I
couldn't be together anymore.
You started to believe
that all bears
were the enemies
of humans.
Obviously.
Bears kill people,
my own mother included.
They are enemies!
You're wrong.
I was just
an unwanted bear,
but you found me
and saved my life.
You approved me
and gave me love.
It's true,
Growl, Growl.
It is not true!
I refused to forget
the love I got
from you that day.
And I refused
to give up
on the love I felt.
That's why
I crossed the wall.
I'm here for you,
Kureha.
I wanted to be
true friends
with you once again.
Really?
That's why you're here?
Don't listen to her.
She's a liar
and a murderer bear.
Think of all the girls
in your class
that she killed.
I wanted to protect
Kureha
from the invisible storm.
I won't forgive
those who try
to exclude her.
I'm a bear.
What else could I do?
Oh, no.
Didn't I tell you
as much?
Bears don't feel
love or friendship.
They're sullied beasts
and that is
their true nature.
Do it already.
Shoot that thing
until it's dead.
But I...
It's okay, Kureha.
I finally understand.
When Lady Kumaria
told me about
the promised kiss,
she was actually
talking about
that bullet
in the chamber
of your gun.
Growl, growl.
What?
I'll accept this
as a criminal bear.
Hopefully it'll prove
to you the love
I have is the real thing.
If this is the only way
to become true friends
with you again,
then I will embrace it.
Do it!
Why are you hesitating?
Punish that criminal bear
right now!
Give me the promised kiss.
I'm ready!
Promise kiss?
From me to you?
And me to you.
Then everything will awaken
and it will all change.
Na-na-na-na-na-na!
Na-na-na-na...
what do you think you're doing i can't shoot don't be absurd
killing her isn't going to bring mom back to me it won't change anything you mustn't forgive her
give this woman-eating bear the bullet of judgment i can't do that how could i when ginkgo was the
one who saved me from the invisible storm she jumped into the fire too she risked her life to
protect sumika's letter for me you fool that beast is just a criminal bear pretending to be pure
i don't care
curry pie
lulu
curry pie lulu knows the truth she found out what ginkgo did to sumika
yes ginkgo committed a grave crime growl
kinkgo is the reason why sumika
how could you ginkgo i'll never forgive you bears
i'll ruin you now everyone
tell me is your love the real thing
you